Guide to the Transgender Erotic Pulp Fiction Collection from an Unnamed Series Numbered TDB
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Transgender erotic pulp fiction collection from an unnamed series numbered TDB
1983-1985
Bailey 20
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
1
29 v.; 18 cm.
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Bailey, Laura E., 1951-
Star Distributors, Ltd
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Scope and Contents
Erotic pulp fiction related to male cross-dressing.
Individual titles (see accompanying list) taken from cover.
Each piece contains 2 separate titles, paged separately.
All individual titles paperbound.
Includes personal ads.
Cross-dressers -- Fiction; Cross-dressing -- Fiction; Transgender people -- Fiction; Sexual dominance and submission -- Fiction; Sex -- Fiction; Erotic stories; Personals -- United States; Erotica -- New York (State) -- New York -- 20th Century; LGBTQ resource; Bailey, Laura E., 1951- -- Ownership
- TDB [Unnamed series]
  - Transvestite incest; Husband in lace, c1983; TDB_1_ (Box 1-15)
    Scope and Contents
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model Dist.
  - Trained she/male; TV serving girl, c1983; TDB_2_ (Box 1-15)
    Price label on front cover: 4--
  - Teenage T.V.; Show-biz she-male, c1983; TDB_3_ (Box 1-15)
  - She-male slut; Abused T.V., c1983; TDB_4_ (Box 1-15)
  - Daddy in lace; Sweet young she-male, c1983; TDB_5_ (Box 1-15)
  - Mama's frilly boy; She-male in heat, c1983; TDB_6_ (Box 1-15)
  - She-male in heat; A TV's secret, c1983; TDB_7_ (Box 1-15)
    Price label on front cover: $3.00
  - She-male nurse; Her husband's secret shame, c1983; TDB_8_ (Box 1-15)
    Stamp on bottom edge: Model D[ist.]
  - The boss' TV mistress; Dressing up her husband, c1983; TDB_9_ (Box 1-15)
  - She-male tycoon; Little brother in lingerie, c1983; TDB_10_ (Box 1-15)
  - Transvestite bondage playmate; She-male M.D., c1984; TDB_11_ (Box 1-15)
    Stamp on top edge: Model Dist.
  - She-male stripper; His mother's she-male slave, c1984; TDB_12_ (Box 1-15)
  - Wearing his wife's lingerie; Daddy in dresses, c1984; TDB_14_ (Box 1-15)
    Stamp on bottom edge: [Mode]l Dist.
  - Jealous TV bitch; She male body slave, c1984; TDB_15_ (Box 1-15)
  - She male on the street; Forced to wear dresses, c1984; TDB_16_ (Box 16-31)
  - Coach's kinky shame; Wearing his sister's panties, c1984; TDB_17_ (Box 16-31)
    Stamp on top edge: MBN [?]
  - Dad's fetish for dresses; Forced into panties, c1984; TDB_18_ (Box 16-31)
  - Pro jock she male; Her man wears panties, c1984; TDB_19_ (Box 16-31)
  - Kinky she male nurse; Rock star's she male shame, c1984; TDB_20_ (Box 16-31)
    "Stamp on top edge: MBN [?] Price label on front cover: $3.00"
  - Daddy in drag; Spread stud in panties, c1984; TDB_21_ (Box 16-31)
  - Her man wears a bra; Mommy's spread she male, c1984; TDB_22_ (Box 16-31)
  - Jock in a G-string; Femme fatale father, c1984; TDB_24_ (Box 16-31)
  - TV on her knees; Sexy spread TV, c1984; TDB_25_ (Box 16-31)
    Stamp on bottom edge: MBN
  - She male bitch; TV trucker, c1985; TDB_27_ (Box 16-31)
  - Stud sissy; Drag queen marine, c1985; TDB_28_ (Box 16-31)
    Stamps on top edge: MBN; MBI; May 03 1985
  - Abused TV; She male street walker, c1985; TDB_29_ (Box 16-31)
  - Blackmailed TV; She male whip mistress, c1985; TDB_30_ (Box 16-31)
    Stamps on top edge: MBN; MBI; Jul 5 1985
  - He-man sissy; She-male in bondage, c1985; TDB_31_ (Box 16-31)
  - Stud in a bra; Her man is a girl, c1985; TDB_32_ (Box 32)